{
    "question": "Make sentences with the words given    1. Seimpi -dance-traditional\r\n 2.Mr.Handoko -teacher-kind\r\n 3. Miss kirana -dancer-famous\r\n 4. Jakarta-city-big\r\n 5. I-boy-strong\r\n 6.Farida-girl-slim\r\n 7. We-stundent-Indonesia\r\n 8. Borobudur-temple-famous\r\n 9. Indonesia-country-big\r\n 10. Wisnu-handsome-boy",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "<p>Jawaban:</p><p>1. Serimpi is one of the traditional dance from Yogyakarta.</p><p>2. Mr. Handoko is a kind teacher.</p><p>3. Mrs. Kirana is a famous dancer.</p><p>4. Jakarta is a big city.</p><p>5. I am a strong boy.</p><p>6. Farida is a slim girl.</p><p>7. We are Indonesian students / We are students from Indonesia</p><p>8. Borobudur is a famous temple.</p><p>9. Indonesia is a big country.</p><p>10. Wisnu is a handsome boy.</p><p></p><p>Penjelasan:</p><p></p><p>hope you find this helpful^\u2022^</p>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "essays-1-give-2-examples-how-to-offering-help-2-what-is-narativ-333",
            "question": "Essays    1. Give 2 examples how to offering help\r\n2 What is \"Narative Text\r\n3. Write 2 sentences using \"should\r\n4. Name 2 examples of \"Quantifiers\"\r\n5 Give 1 sentence of \"Simple Past Tense\"\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>1. Hello,how could i help you?</p><p>   Hey,may i help you with something?</p><p>2.  . . .</p><p>3.You should go to bed now,Nathan.</p><p>   i think you should get some rest</p><p>4. . . .</p><p>5 . . .</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "iil-arrange-these-words-to-make-good-sentences-susunlah-kata-ka-116",
            "question": "IIL arrange these words to make good sentences! (susunlah kata-kata di bawah ini menjadi    kalimat yg benar)\r\n9. You - are - where - from - ?\r\n10. Name - is - what - your - ?\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>where are you from</p><p>what is your name</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>semoga membantu</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>9. Where are you from?</p><p>10. What is your name?</p><p></p><p>tolong jadikan brainliest answer yaa makasih:D</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "38-a-part-of-songs-which-tells-the-story-is-called-a-chorus-b-246",
            "question": "38. A part of songs which tells the story is called..    A. Chorus\r\nB. Pre-chorus\r\nC. Verse\r\nD. Coda\r\n\r\n39. A part of songs which is also called as tail is.. \r\nA. Chorus\r\nB. Pre-chorus\r\nC. Verse\r\nD. Coda\r\n\r\n40.A part songs which usually repeated in a song is... \r\nA. Chorus\r\nB. Pre-chorus\r\nC. Verse\r\nD. Coda\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\nBantu jawab\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>38.C. Verse</p><p>Penjelasan=<u>A\u00a0verse\u00a0is a repeated section of a\u00a0song\u00a0that typically features a new set of lyrics on each repetition. ... And while choruses typically contain a\u00a0song&#039;s\u00a0signature\u00a0musical\u00a0motif, the\u00a0music\u00a0of a\u00a0verse\u00a0is often written to complement the chorus\u00a0music.</u></p><p></p><p><u>3</u><u>9</u><u>.</u><u>D</u><u>.</u><u> </u><u>C</u><u>o</u><u>d</u><u>a</u></p><p><u>p</u><u>e</u><u>n</u><u>j</u><u>e</u><u>l</u><u>a</u><u>s</u><u>a</u><u>n</u><u>=</u><u>Coda is an Italian word for \"tail,\" it is the additional lines of a\u00a0song\u00a0which brings it to a close. The coda is an optional addition to a\u00a0song.</u></p><p></p><p><u>4</u><u>0</u><u>.</u><u>A</u><u>.</u><u> </u><u>C</u><u>h</u><u>o</u><u>r</u><u>u</u><u>s</u></p><p><u>p</u><u>e</u><u>n</u><u>j</u><u>e</u><u>l</u><u>a</u><u>s</u><u>a</u><u>n</u><u>=</u><u>When a distinction is made, the chorus is\u00a0the part\u00a0that contains the hook or the \"main idea\" of a\u00a0song&#039;s\u00a0lyrics and\u00a0music, and there is rarely variation from one\u00a0repetition\u00a0of the chorus to the next</u></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "siang-dia-1-malam-dia-2-apakah-saya-119",
            "question": "Siang dia 1 malam dia 2\r\n\r\n\r\napakah saya??\r\n \u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>makhluk jadi jadian </p><p>karena sejujurnya saya tidak tahu jawabannya</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "7-where-is-wahyu-going-a-to-library-b-to-laboratory-c-to-can-988",
            "question": "7. Where is Wahyu going?\r\na. To library\r\nb. To laboratory\r\nc. To canteen\r\nd. To parking lot\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>bacaannya tentang apa?? bilang di komen ya, biar aku jawab, ini kurang jelas kak</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>a. to library</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>semoga membantu</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "33-rearrange-these-sentences-into-a-good-paragraph-1-jack-had-564",
            "question": "33. Rearrange these sentences into a good paragraph!    (1) Jack had an accident a few days ago\r\n(2) Jill went to the Hospital to visit him\r\n(3) He is still in the hospital now\r\n(4) She is at hospital now\r\n(5) He had to go to the hospital\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>(1),(5),(3),(2),(4)</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>1.jack mengalami kecelakaan beberapa hari yang lalu</p><p>5.dia harus pergi ke RS</p><p>3.dia(laki laki) masih di rumah sakit sekarang</p><p>2.jill pergi ke RS untuk mengunjunginya(laki laki)</p><p>4.dia(perempuan) di RS sekarang</p><p></p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "fill-in-the-blanks-with-tobe-am-is-are-for-example-my-moth-393",
            "question": "Fill in the blanks with tobe (am/ is/ are).    For example : My mother ... beautiful.\r\n My mother is beautiful.\r\n (She)\r\n1.My friends ... in the library.\r\n\r\n2.I and my brothers ... at our uncle home.\r\n\r\n3.My sisters ... diligent and smart.\r\n\r\n4.My aunts ... kind and beuatiful.\r\n\r\n5.The tiger ... wild.\r\n\r\n6.The sharpener ... sharp.\r\n\r\n7.Anton and Andi ... in the field.\r\n\r\n8.My niece ... still baby.\r\n\r\n9.The teachers ... in the classroom.\r\n\r\n10.My grandmother and my grandfather ... at our home.\r\n\r\npliss dijawab\r\n\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>1. is</p><p>2. are</p><p>3. is</p><p>4. is</p><p>5. is</p><p>6. is</p><p>7. are</p><p>8. is</p><p>9. are</p><p>10. are</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "7-which-of-the-following-statements-kinds-of-weather-put-a-chec-509",
            "question": "7.    Which of the following statements kinds of weather? Put a check mark () in the box in front of th\r\nstatements for correct answers.\r\n1. O Sunny\r\n4. O Rainy\r\n2. Windy\r\n5. O Dry\r\n3. Foggy\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Sunny \u2705</p><p>Rainy \u2705 </p><p>Windy \u2705</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>ituu yyaa</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "2-menulis-minimal-5-kalimat-possitive-degree-ttg-benda2-di-rumah-544",
            "question": "2. Menulis minimal 5 kalimat possitive degree ttg benda2 di rumahmu.    3. Menulis minimal 5 kalimat comparative degree ttg benda2 di rumahmu\r\n 4. Pilih 5 pertanyaan d bawah ini, jawablah dengam kalimat superlative degree.\r\n Questions\r\n 1. Which flower has the most /the worst fragrance?\r\n 2. What is the longest/shortest river in the world?\r\n 3. Who is the heaviest/lightest man in the world?\r\n 4. Which is the smallest/biggest animal in the world?\r\n 5. Which animal does have the slowest/fastest movement?\r\n 6. What is the cheapest/the most expensive thing in the world?\r\n 7. What is the most popular activity during pandemic?\r\n 8. Who is the oldest man in the world?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>2. Menulis minimal 5 kalimat positive degree ttg benda2 di rumahmu.</p><p>a. My smartphone is <strong>as sophisticated as</strong> my laptop.</p><p>b. My car is <strong>as expensive as</strong> my uncle&#039;s car.</p><p>c. My bicycle is <strong>as new as</strong> my neighbor&#039;s bicycle.</p><p>d. My room is <strong>as clean as</strong> a hotel&#039;s room.</p><p>e. My books are <strong>as important as </strong>my professor&#039;s books.\n</p><p>3. Menulis minimal 5 kalimat comparative degree ttg benda2 di rumahmu</p><p>a. My laptop is <strong>more expensive than </strong>my smart phone.</p><p>b. My car is <strong>more expensive than</strong> my motorcycle.</p><p>c. My neighbor&#039;s bicycle <strong>is cheaper than</strong> my bicycle.</p><p>d. My room is <strong>more comfortable than </strong>a hotel&#039;s room.</p><p>e. My books are <strong>more important than</strong> my toys.\n</p><p>4. Pilih 5 pertanyaan d bawah ini, jawablah dengam kalimat superlative degree.\n</p><p>Questions\n</p><p>1. Which flower has the most /the worst fragrance?</p><p>I think Jasmine flowers have the <strong>most fragrance.</strong></p><p>I think Rafflesia Arnoldii has the <strong>worst fragrance.</strong>\n</p><p>2. What is the longest/shortest river in the world?</p><p>The Nile River is <strong>the longest</strong> river in the world.</p><p>The Roe River is <strong>the shortest</strong> river in the world.\n</p><p>3. Who is the heaviest/lightest man in the world?</p><p>Franco is <strong>the heaviest </strong>man in the world.</p><p>Junrey Balawing is <strong>the lightest</strong> man in the world.\n</p><p>4. Which is the smallest/biggest animal in the world?</p><p><strong>The biggest</strong> animal in the world is Antarctic Blue Whale.</p><p><strong>The smallest</strong> animal in the world is Etruscan shrew.\n</p><p>5. Which animal does have the slowest/fastest movement?</p><p>Cheetahs have <strong>the fastest</strong> movement of all animals.</p><p>Snails have <strong>the slowest</strong> movement of all animals.\n</p><p>6. What is the cheapest/the most expensive thing in the world?</p><p>A Lamborghini is <strong>the most expensive </strong>thing in the world.</p><p>Wheat is <strong>the cheapest</strong> thing in the world.\n</p><p>7. What is the most popular activity during pandemic?</p><p><strong>The most popular activity</strong> during pandemic is making contents on social media.\n</p><p>8. Who is the oldest man in the world?</p><p>Kane Tanaka from Japan is <strong>the oldest man</strong> in the world. He was born in 1903.</p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p><strong>Rumus Degrees of Comparison:\n</strong></p><p><strong>\n</strong>Terdapat tiga tingkat perbandingan untuk kata sifat dan kata keterangan dalam bahasa Inggris, yaitu:\n</p><p>\nPositive degree\n</p><p>\nComparative degree\n</p><p>\nSuperlative degree\n</p><p>\nPositive degree digunakan untuk menyatakan sesuatu dalam keadaan selevel:\n</p><p>\nContoh : I am as happy as my parents. (Aku sebahagia kedua orang tuaku)\n</p><p>\n</p><p>Comparative degree dibentuk dengan menambahkan akhiran \"-er\"\n</p><p>\nContoh : Tony is younger than i am. (Tony lebih muda dariku)\n</p><p>\n</p><p>Superlative degree dengan menambahkan akhiran \"-est\" dan memiliki arti sebagai yang paling sehingga tidak bisa dibandingkan lagi.\n</p><p>\n</p><p>Contoh : I am the youngest person in my family. (Aku adalah orang termuda / yang paling muda di dalam keluargaku)\n</p><p>\nSemoga membantu ya.</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "this-song-is-for-question-no-42-44-flashlight-jessie-j-when-tom-287",
            "question": "This song is for question no. 42-44!    Flashlight\r\nJessie J\r\nWhen tomorrow comes\r\nI'll be on my own\r\nFeeling frightened of\r\nThe things that I don't know\r\nWhen tomorrow comes Tomorrow comes\r\nTomorrow comes\r\nAnd though the road is long\r\nI look up to the sky\r\nAnd in the dark I found,\r\nI lost hope that I won't fly\r\nAnd I sing along, I sing along\r\nAnd I sing along\r\nI got all I need when I got you and I\r\nI look around me, and see a sweet life\r\nI'm stuck in the dark but you're my\r\nflashlight\r\nYou're getting me, getting me\r\nthrough the night\r\nKick start my heart when you shine it in\r\nmy eyes\r\nCan't lie, it's a sweet life\r\nI'm stuck in the dark but\r\nyou're my flashlight\r\nYou're getting me, getting me\r\nthrough the night\r\n'Cause you're my flashlight (flashlight)\r\nYou're my flashlight (flashlight)\r\nYou're my flash\r\n42. What is the song about?\r\nA. The singer's new flashlight.\r\nB. The singer's day after tomorrow.\r\nC. The singer's dark side.\r\nD. The singer's special one.\r\n43. How does the writer feel about tomorrow?\r\nA. Happy\r\nB. Sad\r\nC. Scared\r\nD. Stuck\r\n44. Why does the singer sing this song?\r\nA. To show her feeling about tomorrow\r\nB. To help people overcome their problem\r\nC To ask for help because she is always frightened\r\nD. To express her gratitude to have that someone by her side\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p>Jawaban:</p><p>42. D. The singer&#039;s special one</p><p>43. C. Scared</p><p>44. D. To express her gratitude to have someone by her side.</p><p></p><p>Penjelasan: </p><p>hope this find you helpful ^\u2022^ </p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}